Thank you.
>> A
[applause]
>> hello Bashar.
>> Hi you. Good day.
>> I'm grateful to be here again.
>> Us as well.
>> Thank you. Um my first question is about
um when you talked about the memory time
travel.
>> Yes.
>> And the psychic abilities.
>> Okay. Um so the future basically
as I have understood it it's not set
>> correct it's simply a number of
different probabilities.
All right. Then how so when we are
having that psychic moment or awareness,
we're just uh
>> you are sensing the energy patterns that
exist at the present that might likely
unfold into a greater probability of a
particular future. But if you change
that energy, you've changed the future
probability.
>> Okay?
>> So remember, there's no such thing as a
prediction of the future. There is only
a sensing of the energy that exists at
the moment the prediction is made that
might lead to probabilities if the
energy doesn't change.
>> Okay?
>> You're sensing probabilities,
probability levels.
>> Okay?
>> Yes. Now, if something has a lot of
energy behind it, a lot of momentum,
seems unlikely to change, has a high
degree of probability, then yes, you
say, "Oh, well, your prediction came
true."
But when predictions are made and they
don't seem to come true, that doesn't
mean the prediction was wrong. If the
person was truly sensing the energy at
the time, it may simply be that the
prediction being made known to people
and people going, "Well, we don't prefer
that." Then they change the energy. They
have rendered the prediction obsolete.
That doesn't mean it was wrong to begin
with. They have simply chosen another
course. by being informed of the
prediction, by being informed of the
energy that existed at that moment, so
they can make a choice whether they
prefer to let that energy ride or change
course.
That's what predictions are for.
>> Great.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. So,
>> and not to say, well, you're stuck with
that future. Sorry.
>> That's good actually. It's great.
>> Yes.
And so I think a gentleman uh earlier
talked about it but it wasn't clear to
me
>> where we talk about um healing.
>> Yes.
>> And going back and reversing it or
changing it as well but
>> you're not really reversing it in a
sense. What we're saying is
>> do you understand the concept that you
do shift to parallel realities every
moment?
>> Yes. And do you understand that when you
do that, you actually are a different
person in a different reality?
Literally. Even if you think you look
the same, you're not the same person
literally. Do you understand that
concept?
>> Yes.
>> So if you're not the same person
literally,
then you can't have the same history.
It just goes with the new person you
are. That you have to have had a
different history to become the person
you are now. So you are changing your
history so that it makes sense. The
history has to make sense linearly for
you in order to say well now I see how I
became this person because that history
leads to me being this person. Whoever
was there before had a different history
and that's not you.
>> Can we make can I give an example?
>> Yes. Medical science.
>> Yes.
>> You understand?
One personality can have a disease,
another personality in the same body
doesn't because it's not the same body.
Literally not the same body. You may
think it is, but it's not.
That's an example of it. Does that help?
>> Something's still missing for me.
>> Oh. All right.
>> How do we
>> One moment? Yeah.
>> Let's continue with that example. Do you
understand that that has already
actually been physically measured on
your planet?
>> Yes. A person with what is called
multiple personalities, one personality
may actually have a cancerous tumor.
When it shifts personality, the tumor is
not there at all. Is that clear first of
all?
>> Yes.
>> All right. So now think about that.
Someone who has a cancerous tumor, there
had to be some time spent for the tumor
to grow to that point. Yes.
>> Yes. So if the next personality doesn't
have the tumor, what happened to the
time?
Where did the time go?
It's not there, is it?
>> Yeah. It's not going to
>> Is that making more sense?
>> Yes.
>> So that means that it's not the same
timeline. It's not the same history.
It's not the same past because the time
it took, the time that was needed to
build the tumor doesn't exist for the
person that doesn't have a tumor.
>> So the key is changing the personality.
>> The key is knowing
>> that you are a different person every
moment. It's not learning to do
something you're not already doing. It's
becoming aware of what you're already
doing. You are literally a different
person every moment. Literally, this
isn't a metaphor.
You may again look in a mirror and
think, "Oh, well, I look the same as I
did yesterday." You're not the same
person. You just think you are because
of the illusion you've accepted called
continuity in order to play the game of
space-time reality on Earth. But you're
breaking continuity more and more
consciously.
Therefore, one day you may look in the
mirror and go, "Ah, who's that?"
[laughter]
Oh my goodness. Have you ever heard of
or had the experience, and I don't mean,
okay, you haven't seen me in a hundred
years. Yes, I look different. I mean,
have you ever heard of or had the
experience yourself where maybe only a
couple of months or a few months have
gone by and you run into a friend and
the friend goes, "Oh my goodness, I
didn't even really recognize you. You
look so different. What happened?"
>> Yes.
That might be sometimes, not always, but
that might be sometimes the result of
the fact that you actually have changed
yourself sufficiently that you've broken
continuity with your agreement with them
to some degree and are saying, "I'm not
really playing quite by the same rules
anymore."
And they are allowed to recognize that
because that's part of the rules you are
playing by is that they recognize the
break in continuity and realize that you
don't look the same anymore.
that can happen.
>> Do you for uh let's say for a cancer
patient, do they need to actually go and
um I mean go within and realize and
recognize where it came
>> not necessarily. Maybe it depends. You
have to take it on a case by case basis.
Everyone's different about how they need
to get to that realization. And also
remember sometimes people will choose to
have that experience for a very positive
reason and won't let it go.
So again you have to respect the reason
why it was created to begin with before
you can say well let's figure out how to
get rid of it. It may not be get ridable
for a variety of reasons. they may
actually need to hold on to it for a
variety of reasons you have no
understanding of and perhaps no business
trying to change.
You have to explore what's happening
here with this person. What's the reason
this is happening? Is it the result of
negative beliefs they could change and
then change their experience? Or is this
being created for some reasons I can't
even fathom because they're on such a
different path?
Maybe it has to do with the people that
they're interacting with and what those
people go through and how they change
because they have to deal with the
person who has cancer. Maybe that person
is doing it for them. Who knows?
>> Okay.
>> You have to get into every single case
study. They're all different. There are
as many reasons for doing that as there
are people who experience it.
>> Okay.
>> Yes.
>> On a similar note, I just uh remember a
question. Did Tesla create um a healing
um
>> machine
>> machine?
>> Yes,
>> it did.
>> And uh it's not it's not allowed to be
used right now or or
>> the technology is findable. The
technology is doable. It has to do with
frequency, vibration, understanding what
the vibration of different diseases are
and knowing how to apply certain
frequencies to them that cancel that
vibration of the disease out.
>> Mhm. So, it's doable
in a sense. Even though some of Tesla's
papers may have been taken by certain
individuals who didn't necessarily
prefer that the general public
understand some of the things that he
did, that technology is not necessarily
that sophisticated.
>> Did he have any help
from the
>> You all have help. You all have
guidance. But understand he was an
extremely tapped in and talented
individual who had extradimensional
abilities.
Do you understand how he utilized what
you typically call hallucinations?
>> Oh no, I'm not aware of that.
>> As a child, he experienced
hallucinations so real he could not
necessarily tell what was physically
real and what was in his mind.
He actually over time learned to control
that ability
to the point where he could actually
construct
in front of his eyes as if it were
physical
the devices,
see them operating.
If they didn't seem to operate properly,
he could literally act as if he was
taking them apart physically, look at
where the problems were in the
hallucination, repair them in his mind,
put them back together, and then all he
had to do when he built the device was
copy the hallucination, and that's why
his devices worked perfectly the first
time when he built them.
That's the ability that he had. You all
have that potential if it's relevant for
you to experience it. But you all might
experience it in different ways.
Nevertheless, the idea of using
frequency to heal diseases is something
that's relatively easy for you to
accomplish. And in fact, there are many
people actually investigating that
already on your planet. So, do your own
research.
>> Yes.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes. I have one more question.
>> Do you?
>> Yes.
>> Well, I may or may not have one more
answer, but we'll see. [laughter]
>> This I'm just curious. It just I
remembered few nights ago I had a dream.
>> Yes.
>> Which I really don't understand.
>> And
>> um I had I saw that a loved one was
sitting and over his head but not
directly on the top of his head. So
>> yes. Yes.
>> It was as if there was a hologram.
>> The holographic image.
>> Yes.
>> Of uh
it's so hard to explain. like a
holographic image of like a witch's nose
or something like that.
>> Yes.
>> But inside of that it was like as if it
was transparent. There was a skull.
>> Yes.
>> It didn't feel good to me in that, you
know, in that moment. So I just tore it
apart.
>> You tore it apart.
>> Yeah. So what was it?
I really don't understand that
>> you were given an opportunity to learn
to become more lucid in your dreams and
change the outcome of something you
didn't prefer into something that you
did.
>> You're working with a guide that's
helping you understand how to become
more aware while you're in the dream
state.
>> Mhm.
>> All right.
>> So, I did actually change something.
>> Yes.
>> Was that on a template level or
>> in a sense? Yes. The reverberations can
go into the template level from what you
did. Yes.
So congratulations.
>> Thank you. [laughter]
>> Thank you.
>> I appreciate it.
>> Thank you. [applause]
[applause]
>> Hi Bashar.
>> How are you? Good day.
>> Um
I was hoping you could speak on a recent
experience. What I perceive to be my
year. what you perceive to be
>> this year that I experience.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. All right.
>> So, it seems to be a lesson in darkness.
>> All right. And what would that be?
>> Usually, I'm very connected to my
guides. I can hear them. I can feel
them.
>> Yes.
>> And I know they're still there.
>> Yes, of course they are.
>> But this year, I experienced
a lot of darkness. So, one thing after
another. And
>> Yes. All right. And
>> the biggest thing was feeling
disconnected.
>> Oh, all right. And yet you know that you
cannot be. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> All right. You are using your connection
to have an experience of disconnection.
>> Yes.
>> All right. But that means you're strong
enough to handle it now. That's why
they're taking the training wheels off.
>> Yes. So I'm curious now.
>> Yes.
>> Obviously I'm learning a lot about the
power of the darkness
>> and the power of the light within you.
>> Yes. that can balance with the darkness
to put you in the center point. That's
what you're learning here.
>> Okay. So, how can I use that
understanding and apply it with other
people? Like you were talking about
before that you really have to explore
it, right? So, it's like
>> yes,
>> some people need to change a belief, but
other people they need to experience
that circumstance because it's
benefiting them.
>> Well, how does your imagination say you
could use this? How does your
imagination say you could apply this in
positive ways that you prefer in your
life? How can you use this knowledge?
>> I guess realizing that no matter how
much you don't know, you do know on some
level
>> you do. And the first thing you know is
that you don't know everything.
>> Yes.
>> And therefore, you're willing to stay in
the center and let that knowledge flow
through you.
>> Yeah. And allow yourself to know that by
staying in the state you prefer, you
will filter that energy and filter that
knowledge in all sorts of positive
synchronicities in your life.
Yes.
>> And as you get more comfortable with
that or you understand that more,
>> can you almost feel safety and comfort
in the darkness?
>> Yes.
I can put it to you this way. Perhaps
when you get in touch with the darkness
within yourself fully, you know, no
darkness can harm you
because you're equal to it.
>> Wow.
>> To put it euphemistically in Earth
terminology,
no one is as much of a badass as me.
So, I don't have to worry about being
accosted by badasses.
[laughter]
>> I like that a lot. Do you understand?
>> Yes.
>> You are equal to the darkness.
Therefore, darkness cannot touch you.
>> Wow. That's extremely helpful.
>> Yes, it is.
>> Um, okay.
This is kind of a question, but more I
want to know your opinion.
>> Yes.
>> So, there's two very common ideas out
there with spirituality. There's going
with the flow, following your
excitement, a lot more bashari, if you
will. I think I've heard of him.
>> And then there's kind of the Elon
perspective. Obviously, you know, Elon,
um,
>> you're 100% creating your reality. You
can create knowingness and tap into any
reality at any given moment.
>> Yes. Well, there's no difference between
those two.
>> Can you explain that a little bit?
>> What's the difference that you're
perceiving between them?
>> Okay. So, for example, this year that I
had this year of darkness,
>> yes,
>> I didn't plan on it. I'm not saying you
had to plan on it, but you're obviously
creating it for yourself.
>> But I don't feel as if I created it.
>> I don't care if you feel as if you did.
You did. That's the point. You have to
own it in order to be able to use it
effectively. If you don't own it, if you
deny that you had anything to do, if
you're not responsible for creating it,
how can you use it? You can't change
what you don't own.
>> So, is it just a difference of the level
that I'm realizing I'm creating it? For
example,
>> yes,
>> I understand when I change a belief
>> that the synchronicities that follow
that I'm creating that I felt like I
create that.
>> You have to know you're creating it
whether you feel like you are or not
because there is no other way it could
manifest in your life. You have to know
that.
>> So what's the difference between for
example if I stood here right now and I
said I want to be someone else.
want,
>> okay,
>> is not need.
That's your ego talking. Your ego saying
what's happening is not good enough.
Invalidation. I want to be somewhere
else. Why? Did you hear me earlier say
there's nowhere more important than
being here and now with what's
happening?
>> Yes.
>> Then why would you want something else
to happen unless you're invalidating
what's happening?
>> And is that the same for your reality,
too? So
>> we don't invalidate though.
>> We understand that everything that we
experience is part of our creation for
serving us in the best possible way. We
never question that and therefore we
always get the benefit of it. Remember,
even if something manifests,
you can recognize, [clears throat]
you can objectively neutrally recognize
that what manifests may not be what you
neutally objectively don't prefer. But
that's not the same thing as judging it
as invalid. And the idea is if you
understand that something has manifested
that you objectively don't prefer, you
still have to go back into knowing that
still had to happen for a reason that
does serve me. What could it be? So you
start using what you don't prefer in a
way that you do prefer and therefore
what you don't prefer has served you
because it's got to be there for a
reason. It's got to be there for your
reason if only if only to simply
reinforce within you that you have the
ability to use it negatively or
positively. And sometimes you people
will test yourselves. Have I really
changed? Do I really understand how this
works? Let's see. Let me manifest
something I don't prefer and see if I
respond positively or if I still react
negatively, which means I haven't
changed.
So I tested myself and I have reacted in
a way I don't prefer. Therefore you have
learned a valuable lesson.
Therefore it has served you in a
positive way. That's how you need to
look at it.
>> Yes.
>> It's not about what you want to be
different. It's about how willing you
are to use what you've manifested in the
best possible way. Remember. Please
remember. Please remember or don't.
It doesn't matter what happens.
It only matters what you do with what
happens.
>> Would you like to repeat that? It
doesn't matter what happens. It only
matters what you do with what happens.
>> That's it. Period. That's the entire
secret of the instruction manual.
So I don't have to actively
create my desires if I just follow the
flow.
>> If you follow the flow, your needs will
always manifest if they are relevant for
who you truly are. There is nothing you
need to do beyond that. The current of
creation, your current in creation
already knows where you need to go.
Surrender is not surrendering control.
Surrendering is surrendering to the
control that's already built into you.
That's why you go with the flow. The
current already knows where you need to
go. You don't need to make things
happen.
making things happen. Believing that you
need to make things happen is resistance
to the current. Everything that's
relevant for you is already contained
within the current's energy. Just go
with the flow. Your life will unfold
naturally. You will respond to it in a
positive way. Synchronicity will abound.
Everything that needs to happen in your
life that's relevant for you to
experience will happen in perfect
timing.
That's all there [clears throat] is to
it. You don't need to make it work. The
machine works. Let it work.
Let it work. Don't stop it by thinking
you know better what should happen here.
No, you don't.
Many of you have to get to the point
where you finally have to admit to
yourself, I have no bloody idea.
>> I experienced that.
>> All right, then go with that. That as
many people on your own planet say is
the beginning of wisdom to know that you
don't know.
>> Yeah.
>> But your higher mind does. Remember your
physical mind is only designed to
experience what's happening.
It doesn't have any other job. It's not
capable of performing any other
function. Your higher mind knows what
needs to happen and it speaks to you to
let you know what needs to happen by
manifesting its communication in you as
passion
because passion you're willing to follow
except when you let negative beliefs
stop you.
So stop talking yourselves out of
hearing your higher mind.
That's all you have to do. Stop talking
yourselves out of hearing and listening
and following what your higher mind is
doing to guide you by sending the
communication of passion to you. Here it
is. Follow this. Act on this now. Here
it is. Follow this. Act on this now.
Here it is. Follow this. Act on this
now.
[laughter]
I know better. I don't want to go that
way. I want to go this way.
>> Okay. Higher mind says, "Go ahead. Walk
that path." Oops. Look at that. She fell
into a hole. I wonder why. I was going
to guide her around it, but she insisted
she knew better. So, plop. There you go.
Let me help you up out of the hole now.
Dust you off. Are you willing to listen
to your passion now? No. Still stubborn?
Okay. There's another hole over there.
Go that [laughter] way.
>> Yeah, I learned that one the hard way.
>> All right, but the point is hard or not,
you've learned it.
>> Yeah.
>> So, use what you've learned. Don't
ignore it.
>> Yes.
>> Let it be easy because it is
the path of least resistance.
Remember again, analogy path A to Z.
Some people think it's got to be like
this.
Many paths are actually like this
because those detours are necessary for
you to learn what you need to learn so
you can truly appreciate what's on the
path, what the experience is all about.
Plus, remember this. If this is not your
path,
it's not going to be the path of least
resistance.
If this is the path of least resistance,
you're going to flow along this path
much faster than you ever could on this
path. Because if this is not the path of
least resistance, you're going to meet
resistance. It's going to slow you down.
You're going to be walking through
molasses.
Whereas this person taking what seems to
be the longer route will actually move
along it much more quickly because
there's no resistance. Go with the flow.
It knows where you need to go.
Does this help?
>> Very helpful.
>> Thank you.
>> I'm just going to leave you with a joke
that my friend has been dying to tell
you.
>> Oh, I hope they're not really dying to
tell you.
>> But silly, so I hope it doesn't offend
you.
>> Oh, nothing offends me. or I wouldn't be
working with all of you.
>> No offense.
>> Okay, the joke is
>> Yes.
>> How far is Uranus from Asasani?
[laughter]
>> Are you going to provide the answer or
should I?
>> I'll let you.
>> No distance at all. [laughter]
>> Thank you so much, Bashar. So grateful.
Thank you.
[applause]
>> Hello Bashar.
>> Andy you good day.
>> What is the meaning of love?
>> Love is the frequency of existence
itself.
It means you are always unconditionally
supported no matter what you choose. It
means you are free
to be who you truly are.
>> Okay,
>> that's what it means.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
>> That's very interesting.
>> Yes, it is. [laughter]
>> Anything else?
>> Um,
would you like to share anything fun
about yourself?
When I often take walks on the surface
of my world,
Asani,
a planet similar to your own, but with
no cities, just all nature. You
understand?
>> Yes.
I will often find
that
I will run into
at exactly the perfect moment
someone to tell me something exactly
perfect that I need to know. And that
that someone doesn't have to necessarily
be a member of my species.
It could be a visitor from the stars. It
could be a nature spirit.
It could be a tree. It could be a rock.
It could be a stream.
But in gathering all of those
conversations throughout the course of
the day, I will sometimes find at the
end of the day that when I put all those
conversations together, they actually
blend as different parts of one story
that in and of itself then reveals
something wonderful to me.
That's fun.
>> Very fun. Yes,
>> it's amazing.
>> It is.
Will that do or is there something else?
>> That will be fine.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you, Bashar.
>> Oh. Oh. Oh, by the way.
>> Yes.
>> I love you.
>> Me, too.
>> Thank you.
[applause]
One moment.
Who we were just speaking to? Is
something happening for you within 3
months? Some change?
What would that be?
I'm interested in the technology
raw mentioned in the raw material
known as the prana vacuum. How can we
create
a
prana vacuum [clears throat]
using today's technology?
The so-called prana vacuum is the same
thing as the idea of what you might call
the quantum vacuum. Is the same thing as
the zero point energy concept that many
people are talking about on your planet.
It exists all around you. The technology
exists that you can use to tap into it
in certain ways. Many of the kinds of
things that people have invented that
say it's tapping into the 0 point energy
are not exactly doing so. But the idea
is growing in the consciousness, the
collective consciousness of your planet
until such time as that awareness
evolves into technology that will truly
tap into that prana field, the quantum
field, the void, and whatever else you
may wish to call it. It will allow you
unlimited energy, unlimited flow, and
inexhaustible supply of energy that can
be utilized in a variety of ways. Once
you truly tap into that technology, it
has to do with creating devices of
proper resonance, proper frequencies,
capacitors that vibrate at certain
resonant frequencies that deliver and
transform energy in a certain way, step
it down in a way that you can use with
your technology. We have talked a little
bit about this as a space-time antenna
concept. Three nested spheres separated
by fatio diameters penetrated by antenni
that are insulated from a merka, a
double interpenetrated tetrahedrin in
the center of the three spheres that
resonates at certain frequencies and can
be activated by the introduction of
energy into it and it will output energy
of a higher caliber, a higher level and
a higher frequency tapping into the
quantum field in certain ways. But many
people on your planet, a few of them are
beginning to experiment with this and we
cannot deliver more information about
this device until they have already
achieved what it is we have already
delivered. End of discussion.
>> Hello Bashar.
>> Good day.
>> Uh thank you for having this
conversation with each other in this
way.
>> It is our passion and our pleasure to do
so. What would you like to discuss?
>> Talking about the hybrid children. Um
you've mentioned in the past that
contact between hybrid children and
their mothers will expand over time.
>> Yes.
>> Has this process indeed started on this
timeline? Is there is there an increase
of physical contact between human beings
and the hybrid children?
>> Yes, but in an altered reality, not
necessarily physically on your planet so
much, but in a slightly altered version
of physical reality. And in dream time,
these encounters have increased.
>> Okay. Wonderful.
>> Eventually, it will leak into the
physical reality as you understand it.
>> Although it will still be of a higher
vibration than it is now.
>> Yes. Understand. Yeah. And um I also
wanted to talk to you about suppressed
memories.
>> Yes.
>> During our previous conversation, you've
mentioned that I was visited by the
grace when I also was a child.
>> Yes. And that these experiences are
buried deep within my consciousness.
>> Well, not that deep.
>> Oh, not that deep. [laughter]
You also mentioned that I felt
victimized because my childlike state
was not able to comprehend what was
going on during these visitations.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. And is it correct to say that from
the point of view as a human being child
that these visitations and the removal
of genetic material was somehow
experienced as a trauma on a
psychological level?
>> Yes. But only because of the way you
were raised as a human. Not because it's
innate to the being a child. Not because
it's innate to being a human child. just
because of the way your planet views
these kinds of things and because it is
shortsighted in its compartmentalization
of awareness. That's the only reason you
experienced it traumatically.
>> And is that also the reason that we're
still somehow afraid of
extraterrestrials?
>> Because you are afraid of portions of
your own power and the extraterrestrials
you're encountering represent and
reflect the idea of your true power in
certain ways. Uh I understand and that
[clears throat] yeah that's probably not
a coincidence but that leads up to my
next question. Um
both my parents have transitioned almost
within 3 years of each other and the
last parent my father passed one year
ago.
>> Yes.
>> And their physical absence caused a
shift in my life.
>> Yes. Of course that's the purpose of it.
>> Yeah. Um, I experienced this as a
tremendous opportunity to shed a whole
bunch of negative belief systems that I
have bestowed upon myself through their
upbringing.
>> Well, congratulations. That is a
positive way to use it.
>> Thank you. But I also sense that this
tremendous opportunity is sometimes a
bit frightening.
>> Why?
>> As if this whole new space that has
opened up is sometimes too big to
handle.
>> Impossible. Otherwise, you wouldn't
experience it.
You only grow into the space you're
ready for. So no matter how it looks,
you're making a comparison, still using
some of the outdated beliefs to view it
instead of letting go of those outdated
beliefs and understanding you cannot
experience more than you're ready for
anyway.
You can expand into it. That's why it
looks that big because that's how big
you actually are when you let go of the
limiting beliefs.
>> Mhm. I understand what you're saying.
>> I understand what you're saying.
>> And I also um am aware of the physical
impact of this awareness.
>> Yes.
>> Uh uh for instance, when my body is
sleeping,
>> Yes.
>> it seems to respond to this awareness
with an actual physical shock during the
night that eventually wakes me up.
>> Yes, it can. Because again your body is
not used to the vibration or frequency
of energy but it can get used to it over
time.
>> And how how how can we do that? Can you
say something about um how to to
integrate this new space and the
awareness of new space and the physical
response to this? Is it just going with
the flow, letting it happen?
>> That's one way practice in a sense
having it happen over and over again.
You'll get used to it. That's one way.
But one way to accelerate that is to
understand or have a perspective
where physical reality isn't really
separate from spirit reality. It's
really not so different. It's just that
you've defined it as very different.
You've placed certain definitions on
physical reality that makes it seem so
unlike spirit reality when in fact it's
a natural extension of it.
>> Okay? and the and the and the and the
physical body that reacts um um how can
we smoothen that out? Well, this is what
I'm telling you. Stop making such a
separation in your belief system between
the idea of your physical body and your
spirit. Your physical body is your
spirit in physical terms. Mhm.
>> It's the same kind of idea, if you wish,
a crude analogy of saying
ice is still water.
It's just frozen,
>> but it's the same thing. It's the same
substance essentially, and so is steam.
So if you start looking at your body as
if it's simply euphemistically a frozen
version of your spirit or at least a
portion of your spirit, you can start to
allow the physical reality to sort of
melt a little bit more,
>> allow it to become a little bit more
fluid, a little bit more liquid and not
be so different from the liquid version
or the steam version. So you have to
start really looking at physical reality
as if it's just another state of being
of spirit and not really separate. It's
the idea of separation that's tripping
you up.
>> Yeah, I understand. Understand. And um
you also said something about um that
the human beings on earth will become
more and more human over time.
Yes. You're actually not fully human
yet.
>> Yeah. And I was wondering what you meant
by that. What does it mean to be human
as opposed to not being fully human?
>> Being fully human means that you
understand that everything is made of
unconditional love. You understand that
everything is connected. Everything is a
reflection of everything else and you
act accordingly.
>> Mhm.
Yes. Being fully human is what you
ascribe to beings like Christ, Buddha,
Krishna, so on and so forth. It's the
idea of the behavior that reflects the
godhood within you.
>> Yes.
Yeah. And that probably also means that
um we're not so compartmentalized in our
way of thinking then.
>> Exactly. You think more holistically,
more as a whole system. That's why I
said you understand everything is one
thing. I am you from another point of
view. Literally, I am you from another
point of view. You are us from another
point of view. A fully realized human
lives
in that truth.
>> Yeah. Thank you so much, Bashar.
>> You are so welcome. Ao.
>> Ao.
Greetings Bashar. I have a question for
you. What is the template level of our
space-time reality? You've mentioned
that there is a template level and that
we are each exploring themes
from this template level that there is a
specific template for our lives. I'm
wondering if this template is actually
revealed in the deck of what we consider
52 playing cards. And if this template
level of reality is expressed,
symbolized in the deck of 52 playing
cards, where exactly did these cards
come from? Who created them and when?
And what is the best way for us to
utilize these cards now in our lives in
order to explore the theme of our lives?
play our cards right and give ourselves
permission to be our best self. Thanks
Bashar.
>> All 52 are symbolic of the template
level because it can be mixed and
matched in any number of ways. It's not
any one card. It's all of them that
represents and symbolizes the template
level which is created by the choices
you make in spirit to have a physical
experience. So as above so below. You
use the energy of the consciousness
field to arrange
certain kinds of blueprints that will
manifest physiologically as the theme
you will explore in physical reality.
And the idea of any kind of permission
slip like a normal deck of cards or
tarot cards or any kind of divination
system represents to some degree the
idea of the template level. Now you have
some freedom in that with your free will
as to how you experience the template
you laid out for yourself. And sometimes
some things can be altered or shifted.
But in general, the choices made by you
as a spirit will be played out as the
cards you are dealt. But you can shift
them around a little bit here and there
with your free will. But you will play
that game. That's what you decided as a
spirit. So that's how the cards
represent the idea of the template level
in energy that then becomes crystallized
down in frequency down into what you
experience as the physical card game
that you are playing. Playing the right
cards, as you say, is easy when you
simply follow the formula. That's the
secret to playing your best hand.
>> Hey, how are you, Mr.?
>> Perfect. And you?
>> Yeah, I'm fine. Uh let's see. My
questions are
um are feelings or thoughts the higher
priority for manifesting our reality?
Because it seems like
uh unresolved feelings manifest over our
thoughts. So how are they linked? And
this is how it works. First you begin
with beliefs and definitions. What you
believe to be true is reinforced by the
idea of feeling that it is true,
thinking that it is true, and behaving
as if it is true. Belief systems use
feelings, emotions, thoughts, and
behaviors to reinforce the validity and
the reality of the belief system because
physical reality isn't really real.
Therefore, beliefs have to make you
believe that it is real. And they do so
by reinforcing what you believe to be
true with the idea that it feels true.
You think it's true and you behave as if
it's true. That's the priority. That's
the order in which it happens. You
cannot have a behavior. You cannot have
a thought and you cannot have an emotion
without first believing or defining that
something is true for you. Beliefs are
the blueprint that allow you to build
the house of your physical reality. So
it all starts with that. So when you
behave a certain way, when you think
certain thoughts, when you feel certain
emotions, they all go back to what must
I believe to be true about myself in
order to feel, think, and behave this
way. Does that help you?
>> Yeah. So [snorts] if I want to change
the belief system, uh the action or how
I behave would be the best way to start
and then the feelings and thoughts.
>> You can start from any direction you
wish. But in a sense, the most efficient
way to change a belief system is to
figure out what that belief is telling
you. Figure out why you're buying into
it because it may simply be a habit that
you have because you've been taught to
believe this way. It may be that you're
getting something out of believing that
way because you don't hold on to any
belief you don't think serves you. So
even if it doesn't seem to serve you,
you may have a belief that says that the
alternative would be worse than holding
on to the beliefs you have even if
they're not comfortable because you all
want to believe that everything needs to
serve you, which is true. It can. But
sometimes you have beliefs and you hold
on to them even if you know they're not
the best beliefs to hold on to because
you have a belief that the alternative
would be worse. And therefore, you'll
still hold on to whatever it is you're
holding on to until you change until you
understand that the idea that something
worse will happen if you behave more
like your true self is a fallacy. So you
have to examine why the belief is there
to begin with. Allow yourself to
understand why you're buying into it and
be honest in your self-investigation of
what you believe will happen if you
actually go in a direction you say you
would prefer to. Once you understand
that a negative and fear-based belief is
simply telling you a story that isn't
necessarily true, then you can see that
it is nonsensical and illogical. And as
soon as it is nonsensical, you will drop
it because you don't hold on to things
that don't make sense. If you do hold on
to things that don't make sense, it's
because you have a belief that says it
makes more sense than the alternative.
>> This is what we call the motivational
mechanism in your psychology as humans.
You always always without fail
move in the direction of what you
believe serves you. You always without
fail move away from what you believe
does not serve you. So if you see
yourself choosing things that you know
intellectually don't serve you, it can
only mean you've defined it and attached
a belief to it that says it's better
than the alternative. It serves you
better than the alternative. Find out
why you believe that. And when you
expose the belief in the story it's
telling you, you will see that it makes
no sense and it will be dropped. It will
be gone.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Yes.
Uh um
let's see uh the next question is uh
from the soul's perspective
um is the physical body like a
radiocontrolled car where you uh the
soul uh puts input to make it go left
and right and then there's always input
also input from the environment. So it's
like uh
>> to some degree you can use whatever
analogy you wish
>> but the idea really is that the physical
world and the physical body is a
projection of the soul's consciousness.
It's like putting on a diving suit. More
than the idea of a remote control car.
It's like putting on a diving suit or a
diving mask and going diving under the
ocean. The mask helps you see underneath
the ocean clearly.
It's not designed to tell you what to
do. It's designed to tell you what
you're experiencing more clearly. When
you leave the physical reality, it's
like taking off the diving mask and
going back to the surface.
So, even though you have free will as a
physical being, the soul determines what
the general trajectory is from its own
free will. And that may be what the
physical mind thinks of as destiny. In
other words, you are the person you are.
You will do everything as the person you
are. You cannot actually fundamentally
change the person that you are. Although
the personality can shift to a great
degree, but it's still happening to you
as you think of yourself as a separate
autonomous being. So you have the free
will to experience the destiny of the
soul in any way, shape or form that the
physical mind chooses to. positive,
negative, happy, sad, whatever, fast,
slow, up, down, but you will walk that
path because it was determined by your
free will as a soul. Is this helping?
>> Yeah, the diving suit uh was a much
better uh metaphor than the radio
control car.
>> All right,
>> thank you.
>> Um, two more questions really fast. Uh,
>> yes. who um when uh when a soul wants to
have an experience here on earth and
many souls wants to have an experience
here on earth. Uh who gets gets
priority?
>> There is no need for priority because
there are a multitude of infinite
parallel realities that can have a
similar experience.
>> Uhhuh.
Okay. And then the last question, uh, on
your planet, uh, do you fart and do you
laugh at your own farts like humans do?
[laughter]
>> We laugh, but we don't eat, so we don't
fart.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah. Uh, I think that was
all. Thank you.
>> All right. Thank you. Ao,
>> good day, Bashar. I would like to know
about the Bosnian pyramids. the ones
located in Visoko.
Uh, and like who built them and for what
purpose? And um, yeah, anything you can
tell me about the pyramids
in Visoko in Bosnia.
Thank you.
pyramids around your planet at a certain
time were all built relatively close to
one another in time around your 10,500
years ago.
The idea is that they were energy
collectors to balance the earth that had
gone through a catastrophic change when
it was impacted by a cometary body that
caused the annihilation of your
Atlantean civilization.
And therefore knowledge and energy was
preserved in many pyramids around the
planet. And also they were used as an
energy balancing system to bring the
planet back into alignment so it could
recuperate and heal. There are other
things that they were used for but we
will not go into that right now.
>> Hello
>> and to you. Good day.
>> I'm very excited to be here. Thank you
for for talking to me.
>> It is our passion and our pleasure. What
would you like to discuss? Um, so I've
been I've been following my excitement
more and more since I kind of started to
listen to to you speak and I've it feels
really great and I I've been doing some
like bigger and some smaller changes and
I'm I'm following your advice of this
thing of basically following my
excitement more moment to moment because
there's no like one big thing in that
sense.
>> All right. Now do remember the entire
formula not just follow your excitement.
There's other pieces to it. Yes. Yes.
Yes, I know.
>> All right.
>> Um and I um I think what I'm like one
thing that just as an as an example that
I I was I quit one one job that I I felt
like I was not excited about at all.
>> Um and now I have more free time which
is fun. Um, and then sometimes I
I I get kind of frustrated with myself
because I I feel like I sit there and I
have I know that I have all these
options to to act on, but I don't I kind
of don't know what to do. And I wonder,
>> yes, you do. Yes, you do. Yes, you do.
Yes, you do. The idea again isn't that
complicated. Don't over complicate it.
If you have different options, decide
for yourself which one is not only more
attractive, more exciting than any other
option, but which one can you act on,
which one can you do something about. If
it seems that more than one is equal,
you might as well flip a coin. Remember,
synchronicity comes to bear in this
because if you flip a coin and say, "All
right, heads option A, tails, option B."
And you flip the coin, one of two things
might happen. Let's say it lands on
tails, option B, and you find yourself
going, "Oh, goody." Or you find yourself
going, "Oh, I wish it had been option A
instead. Oh, I wish it had been option
A." Then you will know that that was the
one that was more exciting. or if you do
head down a path that isn't necessarily
the most exciting path for you at that
moment, synchronicity will create
certain circumstances that will turn you
around in the correct direction. That's
how it works. It's an automatic
mechanism. So, you don't have to sit
there and wonder and wonder and be
frustrated. Just act on whatever you are
capable of acting on that contains more
excitement than anything else as far as
you can determine. And let synchronicity
guide you with the red light green light
aspect of its being of its nature which
means it will bring you opportunities
you can act on and take further green
light synchronicity. It will prevent you
from acting on certain things that are
not the correct path for you right now.
Red light synchronicity just like you
follow your traffic lights when you
drive. You understand?
>> So the starting and stopping
>> is the way synchronicity guides you. No,
not right now. Don't act in that
direction. Act in this direction.
Whatever you can act on. And you have to
use your imagination. Be very creative
about the idea of what it means to take
action on something in every way that
you possibly can that has to do with
that thing you say excites you. Even if
you have to simulate the reality, that's
taking an action on it.
Let me give you an example that many
people on your planet have used. There
are many people who you call celebrities
that are famous, but you will hear
stories from many of them that before
they were actually able to literally do
what it is that they now do that they're
famous for, they acted it out. They
simulated it. Even sometimes going so
far for someone who might be a public
speaker in an auditorium or a game show
host or a late night interviewer as to
go into a space, set it up like it's
really happening, even to the level of
putting fake people in the audience,
maybe even just cardboard cutouts, and
doing their routine as if it's really
happening. Because then you're training
your body to get used to the vibration
of the reality of that. And that will
make you attract it more strongly by
doing anything you can to simulate
anything you can to take an action in
the direction of what excites you more
than any other choice. And when we talk
about that, it can also be very simple
things. We don't mean when we say follow
your passion, follow your excitement
that it has to be a grand project or
come with trumpets or be a lifespanning
career. Tada! Here's your passion. No.
Every day you have little options,
simple options. I can take a walk. I can
read a book. I can have lunch with a
friend. I can watch a movie. Just choose
the one that has more attractiveness,
more curiosity, more excitement, even
just the tiniest bit more that you're
able to act on than any other one. And
just do that first. You're still
following your excitement by doing it on
that level. And eventually, it will
usually snowball through synchronicity
to bring you more and more opportunities
to act on your passion in bigger and
bigger and bigger ways. But the point
is, it doesn't really matter if it does
or not because you're still following
your excitement just by making sure that
every day the options you choose are
more exciting than any other option and
taking action on the ones that you can.
That's all there is to it. You don't
have to make it a big mystery or over
complicate it or overthink it. That's
why you're frustrated.
>> So, you're saying I'm frustrated because
I am making it way more complicated.
>> Yes.
Because I feel like sometimes it's it's
literally that I have like an afternoon
off and I'm sitting at home and I I I I
don't know like I'm I I
>> then you're not using your creative
imagination
>> sitting at home. Why are you speaking
with us today? Was this more exciting
than any other option?
>> Yes.
>> Well, you see that wasn't hard. So, what
will you do after this conversation is
over? What are your options after this
conversation is over? What are your
options? Name some.
>> Um, probably go to sleep because it's
quite late here. [laughter]
>> All right. Going to sleep can be
exciting. That's fine. But let's say
it's morning. What would be some of your
options?
>> Um, I usually like go for a walk, go to
workout. Um,
>> do you enjoy those things? Are they
expressions of your passion? Uh,
>> yes, they are.
>> Are you sure? Cuz you kind of hesitated.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I'm sure.
>> All right. Because remember, sometimes
you may be sort of doing what excites
you, but you may not be doing it in the
most exciting way. Because the idea of
following your passion requires every
component of it to also be the most
exciting way. So you can do a thing but
where you're doing it, how you're doing
it, when you're doing it, with whom
you're doing it all have to be of that
vibration or you're not really following
your passion. So you get to decide the
way in which you're actually acting on
your excitement. And isn't that an
exciting thought?
>> It is actually.
>> All right. So, just make sure that
whatever it is you choose to do out of
the options that you have, whether it's
taking a walk or working out, you're
doing it in the most exciting way as a
whole system. All the components of it
are being done in the most exciting way.
And if you can't find that one of the
components is the most exciting way you
would prefer to do it, invent, use your
creative imagination to create your
exciting way of doing it.
>> Yes.
Yeah, I think that that what you just
said with the creative Yeah, that that
actually helps a lot. I've never thought
about it that way that I have the power
to do that.
>> You do.
>> You do. So,
>> if that makes things more exciting, then
you're on the right path.
>> Yeah.
>> Does this help?
>> Thank you. Yeah, that that helped a lot.
Yes, it really did.
>> All right. Does that serve you today?
>> Yes. Then [clears throat] we thank you
for your interaction. Ao,
>> thank you. Have a great day.
>> Of course. Always. You, too. [laughter]
>> Thanks. Bye.
>> Why would I have anything else?
>> Sorry.
>> Why would I choose anything else?
>> Oh, yeah. That's um makes sense.
>> Yes, I [laughter] know. That's why I
said it.
>> So, go see
>> and don't choose what doesn't make
sense.
[clears throat]
>> I will. Thank you so much, Bashar.
>> It's up to you. Thank you.